<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicholas Christopher</title>
    <link>https://nchristopher.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nicholas Christopher</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://nchristopher.me/img/og-banner.png</url>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/img/og-banner.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Nicholas Christopher • [Source](https://github.com/nchristopher/nchristopher.me)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nchristopher.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye, Signal</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/goodbye-signal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/goodbye-signal/</guid>
      <description>Signal was a refreshing take on privacy. It employed strong end-to-end encryption, was open-source, and was something I could genuinely put my trust in.
However, that has changed recently. Signal introduced crypto payments in the latest preview of their app - and it&amp;rsquo;s more or less just a scam. For starters, they&amp;rsquo;re using &amp;ldquo;MobileCoin&amp;rdquo;, which nobody has ever heard of. But the real issue is that the coin is pre-mined, in other words, every coin has already been created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Review</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/ubuntu-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/ubuntu-review/</guid>
      <description>Around a week ago, I decided to finally bite the bullet &amp;amp; switch to Ubuntu. It was relatively easy for me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have many files to transfer (most of my disk space was used by programs), and the Ubuntu installation process is much more user-friendly.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been gradually switching to FOSS services, so using Ubuntu (or pretty much any Linux distro, for that matter) was a no-brainer. I kept using Windows for so long because, for the most part, it worked well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Privacy Matters</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/why-privacy-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/why-privacy-matters/</guid>
      <description>Privacy is one of the most important things we have. But, in the “digital age”, it seems to be slipping further and further away.
Most people have taken convenience over the basic right of privacy. For instance, Google is (arguably) the best search engine out there – it can fetch millions of results in a fraction of a second, usually has exactly what you’re looking for, and has a fairly modern design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your CPU has a Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/cpu-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 01:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/cpu-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s well known that closed-source operating systems (like Windows and macOS) aren&amp;rsquo;t exactly good for privacy &amp;amp; security. There&amp;rsquo;s essentially no way for a closed-source system&amp;rsquo;s code to be verified.
Which is why people concerned about their privacy &amp;amp; security should use Libre operating systems, such as Linux. But that&amp;rsquo;s not where it ends.
The Intel Management Engine Intel&amp;rsquo;s Management Engine (ME for short, which is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be calling it) is a seperate computing enviornment present on every Intel chip since mid 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Open&#34; Web</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/the-open-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/the-open-web/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought that everyone should have a website.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be a big, gigantic project, it could even just be a page that says hello.
Our identities on the internet often only exist on others&#39; websites - like Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook. Having your own website puts you in control, and that&amp;rsquo;s important for an open web.
Not to say social media is necessarily bad - we&amp;rsquo;ve just put too much control in big, for-profit companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Nick! I make open-source software for the internet. My projects aim to be useful to me or (hopefully) useful to others. I’m currently using web-based languages, but I’m looking to branch out in the future!
Here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m working on:
 Quoter - a Discord bot which stores quotes for servers &amp;amp; retrieves them on demand. It supports listing, (randomly) displaying, deleting, and editing quotes! PPS Credentials - a tool for PPS students to generate default credentials for their account.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
