<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicholas Christopher</title>
    <link>https://nchristopher.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nicholas Christopher</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://nchristopher.me/img/og-banner.png</url>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/img/og-banner.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Nicholas Christopher • [Source](https://github.com/nchristopher/nchristopher.me)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 14:58:50 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nchristopher.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Open&#34; Web</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/the-open-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 14:58:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/the-open-web/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought that everyone should have a website.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be a big, gigantic thing, it could even just be a page that says hi.
Our online identities often only exist on others&#39; websites - like Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook. Having your own website puts you in control, and that&amp;rsquo;s extremely important for an open web.
Not to say social media is some horrible thing, but it&amp;rsquo;s quite scary to think just how much control big tech companies have over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your CPU has a Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/posts/cpu-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 01:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/posts/cpu-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s well known that closed-source operating systems (like Windows and macOS) aren&amp;rsquo;t exactly good for privacy &amp;amp; security. There&amp;rsquo;s essentially no way for a closed-source system&amp;rsquo;s code to be verified.
Which is why people concerned about their privacy &amp;amp; security should use Libre operating systems, such as Linux. But that&amp;rsquo;s not where it ends.
The Intel Management Engine Intel&amp;rsquo;s Management Engine (ME for short, which is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be calling it) is a seperate computing enviornment present on every Intel chip since mid 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://nchristopher.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nchristopher.me/about/</guid>
      <description>👋 Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Nick! I write code, sometimes it works. I&amp;rsquo;m currently using a (mostly) web-based tech stack, but I&amp;rsquo;m looking to branch out in the future! I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of privacy &amp;amp; open-source software, so most of my projects reflect that:
 Quoter - a Discord bot which stores quotes for servers &amp;amp; retrieves them on demand. It supports listing, (randomly) displaying, deleting, and editing quotes! PPS Credentials - a tool for PPS students to generate default credentials for their account.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
